LIDIYA DIMITROVA

WEB DEVELOPER







Brunswick, Germany







SKILLS

Technologies:

JavaScript

• HTML5

CSS

Node.js

Databases:

- MongoDB
- NoSQL

JavaScript Frameworks:

• React.js

Version Control:

Git

Others:

- Project-Management
- Figma

PROJECTS

JOB PORTAL JOBSY.

Technologies used:
MERN, Type Script, Tailwind,
Socket.io

HANGMAN GAME

Technologies used:
JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

PROFESSIONAL GOAL

Full stack web developer. Currently a second-semester Computing and Computer Science student, who has just completed a 1-year full-time training course in full stack web development (MERN Stack). Looking for a new challenge to contribute and enhance knowledge and experience.

EDUCATION

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Digital Career Institute GmbH, Berlin

12/2021-03/2023

- Carrying out a one-year full-time training including technologies of the MERN stack.
- Development of several small and a final large practical project to consolidate programming skills
- Participation in English classes as part of the course

WEBDESIGN COURSE

Information Services GmbH, Bulgaria

02/2014 - 09/2014

• Development of Photoshop and CorelDraw projects

PRE- AND PRIMARY SCHOOL EDUCATION (M. A.)

University of Shumen, Bulgaria

09/2010 - 03/2015

- Educator and primary school teacher in English and Art.
- Specialization in primary school innovation and classroom management

LIDIYA DIMITROVA

WEB DEVELOPER

STORE APP

Technologies used:
React, HTML5, CSS3

QUIZ

Technologies used:
React, HTML5, CSS3

LANGUAGES

Bulgarian: Mother tongue

German: Fluent (C1)

English: Intermediate (B2/C1)

CONFERENCES PARTICIPATION

22 BETA Annual International Conference, Varna, Bulgaria

 Presentation of own short story for young children in English

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Baking
- Cycling

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Language High School, Bulgaria 2001 - 2005

• Profile German and English

WORK EXPERIENCE

EDUCATOR AS GROUP LEADER

School childcare – DRK KV BS-SZ e. V., Brunswick 12/2020- 07/2021

- After-school care for children of primary school age
- Accompaniment in the preparation of homework and free activities
- Conducting parent meetings

ACTIVITIES IN THE FIELD OF TOURISM AND TRADE

Various spas and resorts in Bulgaria

07/2005 - 03/2010

- Hotel receptionist
- Cashier
- Secretary